foxcrimeindia.com 2011-11-26

# Foxcrime

This Privacy Policy covers the information Fox Crime Channel ("Channel") collects from the users participating in the contest ("Contestants") hosted on [www.foxcrimeindia.com](http://www.foxcrimeindia.com/) ("Website"). The Privacy Policy is hosted on [www.foxcrimeindia.com/privacy.html](http://www.foxcrimeindia.com/privacy.html) and should be read in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions [www.foxcrimeindia.com/terms.html](http://www.foxcrimeindia.com/terms.html) of the contest. This Privacy Policy is in adherence to Facebook's Statement of Rights and Responsibilities and Facebook Platform Policies.  
The source of the information collected from the Contestant shall be (a) the information available to everyone on the Contestant's Facebook page and (b) the information entered during the course of solving the dummy crime case which is part of the contest.  
Here are our privacy principles:

Providing information to us is your choice. By clicking on the "Connect to Facebook" button and allowing access to the information available on Facebook, you agree to allow us authorized use of your personal information and you agree to abide by the Terms and Conditions [www.foxcrimeindia.com/terms.html](http://www.foxcrimeindia.com/terms.html) of the contest. 

You always have the ability to review the information provided by you, to have your information deleted and to opt-out of receiving communications from us.

**Information Collection and Use**

Our primary goal in collecting information is to help identify you for keeping track of your progress in the game. It is also to enable us to contact you in the event that you are chosen as one of the winners of the contest. After the expiry of the contest period, we will delete your information from our records and also ensure that any agent/third party employed by us deletes your information from their records. You can also have us delete your information earlier from our records by writing to us using the links at the bottom of the page.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

•   As a precondition to participation in the contest, we shall ask you to allow us access to basic information available to everyone on your Facebook account **("Personal Information")**. Personal Information may include, but is not limited to your name, physical location, user ID etc. We shall also be asking you to enter your mobile number and e-mail id on the Website during the course of the game.  
•   We may also collect other information available to everyone on your Facebook page but which do not identify you. Such information may include but is not limited to age, gender, list of friends etc. We may also collect information to track user behavior and preferences for internal analytics. This information is collected through the use of server log files and tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information including cookies ("Non-Identifying Information").

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

The Channel may enable access of user information to an agent or any third party for the limited purposes of the contest only. The Channel is the recipient of all the information and undertakes responsibility for the secure retention of the Personal Information. The Channel shall not publish the information on any medium.  
The name and address of the agencies which shall have access to the user information are:

1\. Star India Pvt. Ltd.  
1st floor,   
Urmi Estate,   
95 Ganpatrao Kadam Marg,   
Lower Parel,   
Mumbai-400013

2\. Ogilvy & Mather (WPP Group)   
Head Office Address : 11 – 14 Floor Oberoi Commerz,   
International Business Park, Oberoi Garden City, Off Western Express Highway, Goregaon, Mumbai   
Please note that Star India Pvt. Ltd. undertakes no responsibility and will incur no liability for leakage of any information provided by the Contestants or for any unauthorized use of such information either by the Channel or by a third party.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement  
The Channel shall cooperate with mandated government and law enforcement agencies or any third party by an order under law for the time being in force to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process, to protect the property and rights of the Channel or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

 **Business Transfers**

The Channel will, in no event, sell your information. However, if the Channel is acquired by or merged with a third party it will continue to use the information along with the application.

**Email Policies**

The Channel may use your Personal Information for a variety of transactional emails for the limited purposes of the contest only. When you are authorizing us access to your information, you are also granting us permission to use your e-mail id for such purposes. 

**Security**

The Channel uses industry standard technology designed to help keep your Personal Information safe. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable security practices and procedures and current Internet security methods and technologies in compliance with Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under. We will also ensure that any agent or third party that we employ complies with the same security standards as us for the protection of your Personal Information.

Your information may be transferred to maintained on computers located outside of your state or country where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those where you live. If you are located outside India and choose to provide information to us, please be aware that the Channel transfers Personal Information to India and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we have procedures and security features in place to try to prevent unauthorized access.  
If you have any other questions about the security of your Personal Information, please contact us using the links at the bottom of the page.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. Your continued participation in the contest constitutes an acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions so we encourage you to visit this page periodically to review any changes.

**Phishing**

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to the Channel. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. 

**Grievance Officer**

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are published on our Website.

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Channel or your dealings with the contest, you can contact us via the links at the bottom of the page, or by writing to [foxcrimeindia@startv.in](mailto:foxcrimeindia@startv.in)

**This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.**
